Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence File, 1964-1999 (Box 11-95)
  - 1976
    - A-Ba, (2 folders)
    - Be-G, (11 folders) (Box 39)
    - H-Mc, (12 folders) (Box 40)
    - Me-Sh, (11 folders) (Box 41)
    - Si-Z, (8 folders) (Box 42)
  - 1977
    - A-Bo, (4 folders)
    - Br-Go, (12 folders) (Box 43)
    - Gr-Lip, (11 folders) (Box 44)
    - Lis-Ri, (12 folders) (Box 45)
    - Ro-We, (11 folders) (Box 46)
    - Wh-Z, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - 1978
    - A-C, (8 folders)
    - D-Hor, (12 folders) (Box 48)
    - Hos-Me, (12 folders) (Box 49)
    - Mi-Shan, (12 folders) (Box 50)
    - Shar-Z, (9 folders) (Box 51)
  - 1979, A-W, (2 folders)
  - 1980
    - A-K, (2 folders)
    - L-Y, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - 1981, A-T, (3 folders)
  - 1982
    - A-Com, (6 folders)
    - Coo-He, (11 folders) (Box 53)
    - Hi-N, (13 folders) (Box 54)
    - O-Z, (14 folders) (Box 55)
  - 1983 (Box 56)
    - A-Fe, (11 folders)
    - Fi-L, (12 folders) (Box 57)
    - M-Sc, (14 folders) (Box 58)
    - Se-Z, (10 folders) (Box 59)
  - 1984
    - A-Bi, (3 folders)
    - Bl-Ha, (14 folders) (Box 60)
    - He-M, (13 folders) (Box 61)
    - N-Z, (14 folders) (Box 62)
  - 1985 (Box 63)
    - A-F, (14 folders)
    - G-La, (12 folders) (Box 64)
    - Le-P, (13 folders) (Box 65)
    - R-Z, (14 folders) (Box 66)
  - 1986 (Box 67)
    - A-C, (11 folders)
    - D-K, (13 folders) (Box 68)
    - L-Sh, (13 folders) (Box 69)
    - Si-Y, (10 folders) (Box 70)
  - 1987
    - A-Ba, (2 folders)
    - Be-G, (12 folders) (Box 71)
    - H-Ma, (12 folders) (Box 72)
    - Mc-Sp, (12 folders) (Box 73)
    - St-Z, (7 folders) (Box 74)
  - 1988
    - A-B, (6 folders)
    - C-Le, (12 folders) (Box 75)
    - Li-Sg, (13 folders) (Box 76)
    - Sh-Z, (8 folders) (Box 77)
  - 1989
    - A-B, (5 folders)
    - C-Ha, (11 folders) (Box 78)
    - He-Me, (12 folders) (Box 79)
    - Mi-W, (14 folders) (Box 80)
    - Y-Z (Box 81)
  - 1990
    - A-Ga, (11 folders)
    - Ge-Mi, (13 folders) (Box 82)
    - Mo-V, (13 folders) (Box 83)
    - Wa-Z, (4 folders) (Box 84)
  - 1991
    - A-F, (11 folders)
    - G-Mc, (14 folders) (Box 85)
    - Me-V, (15 folders) (Box 86)
    - W-Z, (3 folders) (Box 87)
  - 1992
    - A-E, (11 folders)
    - F-L, (13 folders) (Box 88)
    - M-S, (12 folders) (Box 89)
    - T-Y, (4 folders) (Box 90)
  - 1996
    - A-G, (10 folders)
    - H-Ri, (14 folders) (Box 91)
    - Ro-Z, (9 folders) (Box 92)
  - 1998
    - A-Cl, (5 folders)
    - Co-O, (12 folders) (Box 934)
    - P-Z, (5 folders) (Box 94)
  - 1999
    - A-E, (7 folders)
    - F-W, (13 folders) (Box 95)
  - Undated, G-S
  - Unidentified, 1964-1967
- Government Service, 1913-1993 (Box 96-136)
  - Organization of American States, 1956-1980 (Box 96-113)
    Correspondence sent and received, speeches, interviews, photographs, reports, clippings and printed matter.
    Arranged in official and personal files organized alphabetically by topic, name of person or organization, or type of material and therein chronologically. Arrangement within folders is in reverse chronological order as received.
    - Official file (Box 96)
      - Alliance for Progress
        - Correspondence, 1964-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Funding cuts, 1967-1968, undated See also Classified
      - American Effort in International and Cultural Activities, State Department, Washington, D.C., 1968, undated
      - American Foreign Service Association, Committee of Judges, 1967-1969, (3 folders)
      - Annual summary of activities, 1967
      - Argentina, 1967-1968
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Brazil, 1967-1969
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1967-1969, (2 folders)
      - Canada, 1967-1968, undated
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1967-1968, undated (Box 97)
      - Chile, 1967-1968, undated See also Classified
      - Colombia, 1963-1969
      - Council for Latin America, 1966-1969, undated
      - Cuba, 1967-1969
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1967-1969, (2 folders)
      - De facto governments, recognition procedure, undated
      - Democratic National Convention, Chicago, Ill., 1968
      - Dominican Republic, 1967-1968
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Ecuador, 1967-1968
      - Education, 1967-1968
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1967-1968
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1967-1969 (Box 98)
      - Guatemala, 1968-1969, undated
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Headquarters, Washington, D.C., new site, 1966-1968, undated, (2 folders)
      - HemisFair, San Antonio, Texas, 1967-1968
      - Humphrey, Hubert H. (1911-1978), and staff, 1966-1968
      - Huntington Hartford Museum, New York, N.Y., 1967
      - “H” miscellaneous,1967-1969, (2 folders)
      - Institute on Man and Science, 1966-1968
      - Inter-American Bar Association, 1967 (Box 99)
      - Inter-American Committee on Science and Technology, 1968-1969
      - Inter-American Cultural Council, 1967-1969, (2 folders)
      - Inter-American Development Bank, 1967-1968
      - Inter-American Music Festival, Washington, D.C., 1967-1968
      - Internal Revenue Service, 1966-1968, (2 folders)
      - Invitations, 1968-1969
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Johnson, Lyndon B., and White House staff See also Classified
        - 1967, Jan.-Mar.
        - 1967, Apr.-1969, Apr., (3 folders) (Box 100)
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Katzenbach, Nicholas deB., 1967-1968 See also Classified
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Meeting of American Chiefs of State, Punta del Este, Uruguay, 1967, undated
      - Mexico, 1967-1968
      - Military governments, 1967-1969, undated See also Classified
      - Miscellany
        - Classified documents, 1966-1969 See also Classified
        - Organization matters, 1965-1968, undated
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1967-1969, (4 folders) (Box 101)
      - National 4-H Club Foundation of America, 1968, undated
      - New York State Bar Association, 1968
      - Nicaragua, 1968-1969, undated
      - Nixon, Richard M., and staff, 1969, undated
      - Nuclear weapons prohibition, 1967
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Organization of American States Association, 1967-1969
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1967-1969 See also Classified (Box 102)
      - Pan American Development Foundation, 1967-1969
      - Panama, 1966-1969 See also Classified
      - Paraguay, 1967-1968
      - Peru, 1967-1969, undated See also Classified
      - Plaza, Galo, 1967-1969, undated See also Classified
      - Population control
        - International Population Program, Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y., 1967-1968
        - Miscellany, 1967-1968
        - Papal encyclical on birth control, 1968
        - Population Crisis Committee, Washington, D.C., 1966-1969
        - Population Reference Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1966-1968
        - Reports and conferences, 1967-1968
        - State Department, 1968
      - Private investment in developing countries, 1967-1969, undated (Box 103)
      - Proposed charter amendments, 1962-1969, undated, (2 folders)
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1967-1969, (2 folders)
      - Rogers, William P. (1913-2001), 1969
      - Rusk, Dean, 1967-1969, undated See also Classified
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Secretary general, election, 1967-1968, undated (Box 104)
      - Social events
        - Chronological file, 1967-1968, (13 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968, undated
      - Spain, 1967
      - Saint Augustine, Florida, 1967, undated (Box 105)
      - Staff, 1966-1968, undated
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1967-1969, (3 folders)
      - Travel, 1966-1967
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1968-1969
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - United Nations
        - Correspondence, 1966-1968 See also Classified
        - Economic Commission for Latin America meeting, Caracas, Venezuela, 1967
      - United States (Box 106)
        - Congress, 1966-1969, (2 folders)
        - Mission to the Organization of American States established, 1966-1969, undated, (2 folders)
      - Uruguay, 1966-1968
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1967-1968
      - Venezuela, 1967-1968 See also Classified
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
      - Westinghouse Electric International Co., Latin America Advisory Committee, 1967-1968
      - “W-Z” miscellaneous, 1967-1969
    - Personal file
      - Appointment as representative, 1966, undated
      - Clippings
        - 1963-1966
        - 1967-1980, undated, (4 folders) (Box 107)
      - Correspondence
        - Congratulatory letters received, 1966, (3 folders)
        - Letters sent, 1966-1968, (5 folders) (Box 108)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 1966-1968, (2 folders)
          - 1969, undated (Box 109)
      - Interviews, 1956, 1966-1969, undated, (5 folders)
      - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Washington, D.C.
        - Board of Trustees, 1965-1970, undated
        - Friends of the Kennedy Center, 1967-1970 (Box 110)
      - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965-1969, undated
      - Kennedy, Robert F., 1966-1968, undated
      - Knights of Malta, 1965-1970, undated
      - Miscellany, 1962-1967, 1977, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1966, undated
      - Photographs
        - Latin American trip, 1968
        - Miscellaneous, undated, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - Printed matter
        - 1956, 1964-1968, (3 folders)
        - 1969, 1977, undated (Box 112)
      - Scrapbook, Punta del Este, Uruguay, 1967
      - Speaking engagements, 1967-1969, undated
      - Speech-writing file
        - Latin America, 1964-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1961-1968, undated, (2 folders)
        - Quotations
          - 1951-1968
          - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 113)
      - Ward, Barbara (1914-1981), undated
  - Panama Canal Treaties, 1913-1987 (Box 113-123)
    Correspondence sent and received, speeches and writings, reports, draft copies of treaties, clippings, and printed matter.
    Arranged alphabetically by topic, name of person or organization, or type of material and therein chronologically. Arrangement within folders is in reverse chronological order as received.
    - Appointment as co-negotiator, 1973-1978, undated, (2 folders) (Box 113)
    - Buckley, William F. (1925- ), 1977-1978
    - Bunker, Ellsworth, memorial services, 1978, 1984, undated
    - Carter, Jimmy, and White House staff, 1977-1979, 1987, undated See also Classified, (2 folders)
    - Ceremonial exchange of treaty instruments, 1978, undated, (4 folders)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, 1975-1977 (Box 114)
    - Citizens' Committee for a New Panama Canal Treaty, proposed, 1977
    - Clippings
      - 1969, 1975-1977, (6 folders)
      - 1978-1979, undated, (8 folders) (Box 115)
    - Committee of Americans for the Canal Treaties
      - Hammer, Armand, letter sent to prospective donors, 1977
        - A-L
        - M-W (Box 116)
      - Miscellany, 1977-1978, undated
    - Conflict-of-interest issues regarding Linowitz, 1977, undated
    - Congressional hearings
      - 1977, Jan.-Aug., (5 folders)
      - 1977, Sept.-1978, Feb., undated, (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - Cuba, 1977-1981, undated
    - Environmental impact statement, 1977
    - General correspondence See also Classified; See also Oversize
      - 1975-1977, (5 folders)
      - 1978-1979, undated (Box 118)
    - Harman, Phillip, 1977, undated
    - Hong Kong treaties and lease similarities, 1982-1983, undated
    - Jorden, William J., draft of book chapters with comments by Linowitz, 1980-1981, (4 folders)
    - Justice Department, foreign agent registration
      - No. 2222, 1970-1972, undated
      - No. 2440, 1974-1976 (Box 119)
    - Legislation, 1984-1986, (2 folders)
    - McClure v. Linowitz, 1977
    - Miscellany, 1957, 1976-1980, undated See also Classified, (5 folders)
    - Opposition to the treaties, 1977-1978, undated, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - Panama Mission to the United Nations, New York, N.Y., 1975-1977, undated
    - Panamanian Committee for Human Rights, 1976-1977, undated
    - Panamanian-Americans in Action, Brooklyn, N.Y., 1977-1978
    - Press relations, 1977-1978, undated
    - Printed matter, 1913, 1960, 1976-1978
    - Public opinion polls, 1977-1978 (Box 121)
    - Questions and answers regarding the treaties, 1978, undated
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1977-1978, undated See also Classified
    - Religious leaders, 1972-1977, undated
    - Sea level canal, proposal, 1977, undated See also Classified
    - Signing ceremony, 1977
    - Speeches and writings by Linowitz
      - “How We Got the Treaty,” essay and diary, undated
      - Interviews, 1977-1978, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1977, undated, (3 folders) (Box 122)
      - Statement and testimony before Senate Foreign Relations Committee, undated
    - Torrijos, Omar, death, 1981, undated
    - Travel to Panama, 1977-1978, undated
    - Treaties
      - Drafts, 1975-1977, undated See also Classified, (4 folders)
      - Final copies
        - 1977
        - Undated (Box 123)
    - White House briefings, 1977-1978, undated, (2 folders)
  - Middle East Peace Negotiations, 1954-1993 (Box 123-136)
    Correspondence sent and received, speeches and writings, reports, transcripts of press conferences and interviews, clippings, and printed matter.
    - Appointment and confirmation, 1979-1981, undated See also Classified, (5 folders) (Box 123)
    - Background material
      - 1973-1974
      - 1975-1985, (6 folders) (Box 124)
      - 1986-1993, (5 folders) (Box 125)
      - Undated, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Carter, Jimmy, and White House staff, 1977-1984, undated See also Classified, (7 folders)
    - Clippings (Box 127)
      - First trip to Middle East, 1979
      - Second trip to Middle East, 1980
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1988, undated See also Classified, (5 folders)
    - Conflict-of-interest issues, 1979, undated
    - Congratulatory letters received, 1979
      - A-F
      - G-Z, (3 folders) (Box 128)
    - Congressional hearings, 1979-1980, undated
    - Egypt, 1954, 1980-1982, undated
    - General correspondence See also Classified
      - 1971-1980, (4 folders)
      - 1981-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - Glenn, John (1921- ), 1982-1983, undated
    - Israel, 1980-1984, undated See also Classified, (2 folders)
    - Israeli settlements in occupied territories, 1980-1984, undated See also Classified; See also Oversize
    - Jerusalem, 1979-1980, undated See also Classified
    - Jordan, 1980-1983, undated
    - Memorandum of understanding, 1954, 1980, undated See also Classified
    - Middle East Study Group, Brookings Institution, Washington, D.C., 1975-1976, undated, (4 folders) (Box 130)
    - Negotiation talking points, 1978-1980, undated See also Classified
    - Notes, 1989-1990, undated
    - Office staff and functions, 1979-1981, undated See also Classified
    - Palestinian self-rule, 1981, 1991-1993, undated
    - Palestinians, 1980, undated See also Classified
    - Photographs, Israel, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - Plenary statement, 1978-1980, undated See also Classified
    - Press conferences and interviews, 1976-1990, undated See also Classified, (5 folders)
    - Public opinion poll, 1980, undated
    - Reports to the president, 1979-1981, undated See also Classified, (2 folders)
    - Sadat, Anwar, funeral, 1981 (Box 132)
    - Scrapbook, 1980
    - Speeches and writings
      - Articles, 1957, 1981-1992, undated, (3 folders)
      - Diaries and personal observations, 1980-1982, undated
      - Speech file See also Classified
        - 1978-1979
        - 1980-1986, (6 folders) (Box 133)
        - 1987-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 134)
        - Undated, (4 folders); (6 folders) (Box 135)
    - Terrorism, 1985, undated
    - Travel and meeting itineraries See also Classified
      - 1979
      - 1980-1985, undated, (2 folders) (Box 136)
    - United Nations, 1974-1976, undated
- General Office File, 1778-1999 (Box 136-538)
  - Part A, 1778-1967 (Box 136-291)
    Correspondence sent and received, speeches and writings, organizational records, legal files, reports, notes, travel files, personal files, photographs, clippings, and printed matter reflecting Linowitz's work prior to his appointment as ambassador to the Organization of American States in 1966.
    Arranged alphabetically by topic, name of person or organization, or type of material and therein chronologically. Correspondence within folders is filed in reverse chronological order as received.
    - Index (obsolete), 1966 (Box 136)
    - Addresses, undated, (4 folders)
    - Affiliated Young Democrats, New York, N.Y., 1966
    - American Assembly, New York, N.Y. (Box 137)
      - Board of Trustees, 1966
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
      - Meetings, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
    - American Association for Middle East Studies, 1963-1965, undated
    - American Bankers Association, 1966, undated
    - American College Public Relations Association
      - Conference, 1964-1966
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966, (3 folders)
    - American Field Service, 1966 (Box 138)
    - American Heritage Foundation, 1964-1965, undated
    - American Jewish Committee
      - Annual meetings, 1965-1966, (6 folders)
      - Executive Committee, 1966
      - General correspondence
        - 1963, July-1965, Apr., (3 folders)
        - 1965, May-1966, Nov., (8 folders) (Box 139)
      - Miscellany
        - 1964-1965, (1 folder)
        - 1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 140)
    - American Management Association, 1964-1965
    - American Sinteel Corp., 1956-1958
    - America's Town Meeting of the Air, guest moderator
      - Correspondence, 1951-1958, (3 folders)
      - Taxes, 1951, Aug. 28, (2 folders)
      - Youth, 1951, Aug. 7
    - Antitrust law
      - International
        - Clippings, 1956-1958
        - Correspondence
          - 1954, Mar.-1956, Nov., (1 folder)
          - 1956, Dec.-1960, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 141)
        - Miscellany, 1952-1957, undated
        - Writings by Linowitz, 1956, undated
      - National
        - Correspondence, 1953-1966, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1952-1965, undated
      - New York State Bar Association, Antitrust Section, 1957-1960, (3 folders)
      - Rochester Antitrust Symposium, Rochester, N.Y. (Box 142)
        - Correspondence, 1959-1960, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1958-1959, undated
    - Arcuri v. Haloid Co., 1949-1951
    - Argus Industrial Corp.
      - Correspondence, 1948-1952, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1948-1951, undated
    - Aronstein, Catherine, 1962-1966
    - Arts
      - Correspondence, 1966
      - Miscellany, 1964-1966, undated
    - Asia, 1965, undated
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1961-1966, undated (Box 143)
    - Association for Teen-Age Diplomats, Rochester, N.Y., 1960-1961
    - Atherton, May, 1956-1958, undated
    - Atlantic Council of the United States, 1966, (5 folders)
    - Awards, 1958-1966
    - Banks
      - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, New York, N.Y., 1945, 1959, 1966
      - Miscellaneous banks, 1962-1966
      - Rochester Savings Bank, Rochester, N.Y.
        - Correspondence
          - 1955-1958, (2 folders)
          - 1959-1966, (6 folders) (Box 144)
        - Examining Committee, 1957-1965, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1948, 1955-1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 145)
      - Security Trust Co., Rochester, N.Y.
        - Committees, 1962-1966
        - Congratulations on election to board of directors, 1961
        - Correspondence, 1961-1966, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1960-1966, undated
    - Bar associations
      - American Bar Association
        - Annual meeting, 1959
        - Committee on International Control of Atomic Energy, 1951, undated
        - Miscellany, 1951-1962
        - National Conference on Law and Society, Chicago, Ill., 1966 (Box 146)
      - General correspondence, 1951-1966, (12 folders)
      - Miscellaneous bar associations, 1957-1966
      - Monroe County Bar Association, Rochester, N.Y. (Box 147)
        - Committee on Individual Rights, 1953-1955
        - Correspondence, 1949-1964, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1950, 1956-1965, undated
      - New York State Bar Association
        - Antitrust Law Section
          - Correspondence, 1963-1966
          - Miscellany, 1964, undated
        - Committee on International Law
          - Correspondence, 1961-1966, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany
            - 1951-1959, (2 folders)
            - 1960-1966, undated, (1 folders) (Box 148)
          - Subcommittee on World Peace through Law
            - Correspondence
              - Connally amendment, 1959-1960, undated, (2 folders)
              - Miscellaneous, 1958-1965, undated, (7 folders)
            - Miscellany
              - 1952-1954
              - 1958-1962, undated, (3 folders) (Box 149)
          - Taiwan, 1958-1959
    - Benda, Harry Jindrich, 1958
    - Binswanger, Max, estate
      - Correspondence, 1958-1965
      - Legal documents, 1948-1959, undated
    - Bond Stores, Inc.
      - General correspondence, 1952-1961, undated
      - John B. Pike & Sons v. Bond Stores
        - Correspondence, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1944-1951, undated
      - Real estate taxes (Box 150)
        - Assessment history, 1944-1951, undated
        - Correspondence, 1948-1958, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1944-1957, undated, (2 folders)
    - Bricker, John W., proposed amendment to the Constitution
      - Correspondence, 1953-1956, undated
      - Miscellany, 1952-1956, undated, (2 folders)
      - Speeches and writings by Linowitz, 1953-1955, undated
    - Brighton School District, Rochester, N.Y., 1956-1957 (Box 151)
    - Buchwald, Art, 1962-1966
    - Business Equipment Manufacturers Association, 1964-1966, undated
    - Butler, George V., 1953-1955
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1965-1966, (3 folders)
    - Casarett, George W.
      - Correspondence, 1946-1959, (5 folders)
      - Patent applications, 1906, 1914, 1934, 1944-1959, undated, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
      - Civil liberties symposium
        - Correspondence, 1963
        - Discussion papers, 1963, (3 folders)
      - Fund for the Republic, 1953-1963, undated, (2 folders)
      - General correspondence
        - 1962, Oct.-1963, Jan., (3 folders)
        - 1963, Feb.-1966, Sept., undated, (3 folders) (Box 153)
      - Speeches and writings by Linowitz, 1948-1964, undated, (4 folders)
      - Tenth Convocation, New York, N.Y.
        - Miscellany, 1948, 1963, undated
        - Speeches, 1962-1963, undated, (2 folders) (Box 154)
    - Chaos Club, New York, N.Y., 1963-1966
    - Churchill, Winston, Sir (1874-1965), funeral, 1963-1966
    - City Club of Rochester, N.Y.
      - Correspondence
        - 1947-1950, (8 folders)
        - 1951-1958, (12 folders) (Box 155)
        - 1959-1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 156)
      - Miscellany, 1948-1952
      - Speakers program
        - Introductions by Linowitz, 1951-1952, undated
        - Schedules, 1948-1959, undated, (2 folders)
        - Speakers, 1948-1958, undated
          - B-E, (10 folders)
          - F-W, (12 folders) (Box 157)
    - Civil Rights
      - Correspondence, 1963-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, Washington, D.C., 1965-1966, (2 folders)
      - Speeches and writings
        - By Linowitz, 1957-1963, undated
        - By others, 1962-1965, undated
    - Classic Malvern Uniform Corp. v. Mazor, 1955-1958, undated
    - Cleveland, Harlan, 1962-1966, undated
    - Cohn, Herman M. (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, 1949-1965, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1935, 1946-1960, undated, (3 folders)
      - Property dispute, 1932-1957, undated
    - Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government